<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Members on Zalando Research</title>
    <link>https://research.zalando.com/member/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Members on Zalando Research</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>[Imprint](/imprint)  ·  [Privacy Policy](/privacy)   ·  &amp;copy; Zalando SE, 2021</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 19:41:32 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://research.zalando.com/member/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Martin Heusel</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/member/martin_h/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 19:41:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/member/martin_h/</guid>
      <description>Martin studied Computer Science at the Technical University of Berlin where his focus was on Machine Learning, Neural Networks from the beginning. He graduated with a Diploma thesis about using Long Short-Term Memory for protein classification in 2007. He worked as Senior Scientist at the Johannes Kepler University Linz in Austria at the Institute of Machine Learning, supported by a Marie Skłodowska-Curie Fellowship program and as a freelancer for several major companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christian Bracher</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/member/christian_b/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/member/christian_b/</guid>
      <description>Christian Bracher is a Senior Applied Scientist focusing on Computer Vision problems at Zalando Research. He completed his diploma in Physics and his Ph.D. in Theoretical Physics at the Technical University of Munich. Christian went on to perform postdoctoral research in Quantum and Statistical Physics in Germany, Canada, and the U.S. where he was also a member of the Faculty of Physics at several colleges and universities in Pennsylvania, California, and New York.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gökhan Yildirim</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/member/gokhan_y/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/member/gokhan_y/</guid>
      <description>Gökhan Yildirim is an Applied Scientist in the Computer Vision team at Zalando Research. He completed his Ph.D. at École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne (EPFL) in 2015, where he conducted research on text recognition, salient-object detection and segmentation. Before joining Zalando, he worked at a tech startup on photography and developed deep-learning based image-understanding methods. Currently, he pursues research and development opportunities in visual content creation and fashion design that leverage deep generative models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roland Vollgraf</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/member/roland_v/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/member/roland_v/</guid>
      <description>Roland is the Head of Zalando Research and obtained his Ph.D. at the Technical University of Berlin in Machine Learning and Statistical Signal Processing. Roland was integral to the establishment of Zalando Research and has been with Zalando since 2013. He previously worked as Head of Research for GA Financial Solutions GmbH and conducted the development of asset risk models and quantitative trading strategies.Current research interests: Deep Learning, Large Scale Bayesian Inference, Permutation Equivariance</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eric Lindig</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/member/eric_l/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 15:52:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/member/eric_l/</guid>
      <description>Eric studied Public Administration at University Potsdam and joined Zalando in 2015. He takes responsibility for our Research Collaborations with academic partners, Network Partnerships (Project ELISE) &amp;amp; outreach to the academic community (Internship Programmes, Research Fellowships etc.).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kashif Rasul</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/member/kashif_r/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 15:52:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/member/kashif_r/</guid>
      <description>Kashif earned his B.Sc. with Honours from Monash University in Melbourne, Australia, followed by his Ph.D. in 2010 from the Free University of Berlin in the area of Differential Geometry and PDEs. He completed his thesis under the supervision of Prof. Klaus Ecker. Prior to finishing his Ph.D. he worked at the Max Planck Institute for Gravitational Physics (Albert Einstein Institute) on the Cactus Framework, an open-source, problem-solving environment designed for scientists and engineers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Member 1</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/member/calvin_s/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 15:52:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/member/calvin_s/</guid>
      <description>You can write $\LaTeX$ and Markdown here.
Minyae adgnoscitque fugiebat parentis ausum superos huius Ait erili meruisse iactatis omnibus erat Lorem markdownum natis, ipsi ipsi aut relictus saxo comitantibus aegro amori verba fugisse mira mortisque leones! Prior sui liquidissimus leve properandum totidem studio, refert magno, me quibus. Sternitur discordia summaque, si deus in undam et vulnere dirusque est felices pallam miserere curvamine comites. Tegumenque decipit suis, poscitur una dea sumus adnuerant, gerebat est edam plura.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Member 1</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/member/ingmar_s/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 15:52:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/member/ingmar_s/</guid>
      <description>Ingmar Schuster studied computer science and linguistics at the University of Tübingen. He turned to statistics and machine learning during his PhD on natural language semantics at Universität Leipzig. Ingmars research topics are Deep Learning methods of sequence embedding and time series forecasting, Monte Carlo and variational approaches to integral approximation, Bayesian models and RKHS methods. Previously, he was a postdoc with Tim Sullivan and Christof Schütte at FU Berlin and before that with Christian Robert at Université Paris-Dauphine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nikolay Jetchev</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/member/nikolay_j/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 15:52:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/member/nikolay_j/</guid>
      <description>Nikolay Jetchev studied Mathematics and Computer Science at the Technical University of Darmstadt, receiving his diploma in 2007. He completed his Ph.D. in Machine Learning and Robotics at the Free University of Berlin in 2012, teaching as a postdoctoral fellow once his studies were complete. He is currently part of the Computer Vision team at Zalando Research. Current research focus: generative modelling of high resolution fashion images, metrics for measuring perceptual image quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sebastian Heinz</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/member/sebastian_h/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/member/sebastian_h/</guid>
      <description>Sebastian Heinz is a Senior Applied Scientist in the Computer Vision group at Zalando Research. He completed his Ph.D. in Mathematics at the Humboldt University of Berlin in 2008. After his studies, he worked as a postdoctoral researcher at the Weierstrass Institute for Applied Analysis and Stochastics, where he analysed mathematical models in elasto-plasticity. He joined Zalando in October 2014.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
