<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Zalando Research</title>
    <link>https://research.zalando.com/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Zalando Research</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>[Imprint](/imprint)  ·  [Privacy Policy](/privacy)   ·  &amp;copy; Zalando SE, 2021</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://research.zalando.com/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fashion DNA</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/project/fashion_dna/fashion_dna/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/project/fashion_dna/fashion_dna/</guid>
      <description>Research Project by Christian Bracher, Sebastian Heinz &amp;amp; Roland Vollgraf Unlike a brick-and-mortar department store, online retailers like Zalando must use digital representations of their offerings to entice customers. Traditionally, this takes the form of information stored in a catalog database, which collects categorical properties (tags), numerical descriptors (e.g., prices), and images of the items. Although this information is curated by in-house experts, assignments are often subjective (what makes a dress ‘dark red,’ or ‘leisure’?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sample Efficient Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/project/sample_efficient_reinforcement_learning/sample_efficient_reinforcement_learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/project/sample_efficient_reinforcement_learning/sample_efficient_reinforcement_learning/</guid>
      <description>Research Project by Calvin Seward, Kashif Rasul, Ingmar Schuster &amp;amp; Roland Vollgraf Reinforcement learning has seen many successes in the last years, enabling computers to beat human masters at such difficult tasks as Go and Atari games. In addition, reinforcement learning is showing great promise in creating exciting consumer facing technologies such as self driving cars, while also driving behind the scenes efficiency gains with self learning recommendation and pricing systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Learning</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/project/adversarial_learning/adversarial_learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/project/adversarial_learning/adversarial_learning/</guid>
      <description>Research Project by Christian Bracher, Martin Heusel, Sebastian Heinz &amp;amp; Roland Vollgraf Deep learning computer vision models, based on our huge archive of fashion images, already empower various customer-facing AI products at Zalando including recommendations, search, and “complete the look”, a product that generates outfits. We currently face two obstacles in applying our models even further: (1) Models that are trained on Zalando’s highly curated shop imagery don&amp;rsquo;t generalize well to other assortments or customer produced content; and (2) Model performance is tainted by spurious correlations with confounding but irrelevant sources of information inside the Zalando image catalog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robust Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/project/robust_reinforcement_learning/robust_reinforcement_learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/project/robust_reinforcement_learning/robust_reinforcement_learning/</guid>
      <description>Research Project by Calvin Seward When I think of robustness, I think of camels1. Camels thrive in unpredictable, varying environments. Be it hot or cold, sunny or windy, dry or rainy camels are prepared with their hump full of fatty deposits, their thick fur and distinctive nose and eyelashes. It would be nice if reinforcement learning methods were like camels, robust and adaptable.
Yet many reinforcements learning methods are quite fragile, and the resulting policies akin to the Devils Hole pupfish, a cute yet sensitive fish whose only habitat is an isolated, water-filled cavern in Nevada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SWARM</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/project/swarm/swarm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/project/swarm/swarm/</guid>
      <description>Research Project by Roland Vollgraf SWARM Layers are a new approach to build powerful learnable set functions. These are multi-variate function over a set (or population) of entities that exhibit permutation equivariance or invariance, i.e. these functions are explicitly agnostic to the order of entities. Architecture Building bocks for SWARM Layers are SWARM Cells. These are modified LSTM cells that are augmented with an additional input. Together with the network input x and the previous hidden state h they also receive an input p which resembles pooled information over the whole population.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generating High-Resolution Fashion Model Images Wearing Custom Outfits</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/project/fashion_renderer/fashion_renderer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/project/fashion_renderer/fashion_renderer/</guid>
      <description>Team members:  Gökhan Yildirim Nikolay Jetchev Christian Bracher Sebastian Heinz Martin Heusel Roland Vollgraf  At Zalando, we provide high-quality photographs of fashion models wearing the articles in our online selection. These photographs help our customers visualise the garments they browse and enhance their shopping experience.
But what if our customers wish to visualise an individually created outfit? Zalando provides a large and evolving assortment of garments, which makes it infeasible to photograph every possible outfit combination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Determinantal Point Processes</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/project/determinantal_point_processes/determinantal_point_processes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/project/determinantal_point_processes/determinantal_point_processes/</guid>
      <description>Research Project by Leonidas Lefakis (ex-member) Chic, shocking, trendy, or casual, Fashion must never be monotonous. As such, diversity plays a central role in fashion. At Zalando we research such topics, focusing on elegant mathematical models named Determinantal Point Processes (DPPs) that capture notions of both relevance and diversity in a principled manner.
Defined over a fixed ground set $\Upsilon$, for example the articles in the Zalando catalogue, DPPs define a distribution over subsets of $\Upsilon$.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feidegger Dataset</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/project/feidegger_dataset/feidegger_dataset/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/project/feidegger_dataset/feidegger_dataset/</guid>
      <description>Research Project by Leonidas Lefakis (ex-member), Alan Akbik (ex-member) &amp;amp; Roland Vollgraf The FEIDEGGER (fashion images and descriptions in German) dataset is a new multi-modal corpus that focuses specifically on the domain of fashion items and their visual descriptions in German. The dataset was created as part of ongoing research at Zalando into text-image multi-modality in the area of fashion.Unlike other tasks typically encountered in multi-modal learning, in fashion the informative information in the visual data often consists of very fine-grained details that needs to be reflected in the textual descriptions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flair</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/project/flair_nlp/flair_nlp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/project/flair_nlp/flair_nlp/</guid>
      <description>State-of-the-Art Natural Language Processing (NLP) Research Project by Alan Akbik (ex-member) Can we teach machines to read and understand human language? And in the future, can we teach them to perform language AI tasks with little training data, across over 20 different human languages? At Zalando Research, we’re investigating answers to these questions.
We are researching a novel approach that leverages neural language modeling to learn powerful, contextualized representations of human language from large corpora.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personalized Size Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/project/personalized_size_recommendation/personalized_size_recommendation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/project/personalized_size_recommendation/personalized_size_recommendation/</guid>
      <description>Research Project by Abdul-Saboor Sheikh (ex-member) &amp;amp; Urs Bergmann (ex-member) Have you ever wondered what would be the best fitting size of a clothing item that you would like to order online? You may have an idea about the size you generally wear, but this piece of clothing perhaps comes in a different size system or maybe it is a style or category that you have not worn before. Then apart from your own preferences, there may be other factors (such as brand, design, material, manufacturing, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shop the look with deep learning</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/project/shop_the_look_with_deep_learning/shop_the_look_with_deep_learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/project/shop_the_look_with_deep_learning/shop_the_look_with_deep_learning/</guid>
      <description>Research Project by Julia Lasserre (ex-member) Have you ever seen a picture on Instagram and thought “oh wow, I need these shoes”? or been inspired by your favourite fashion blogger and looked for similar products (for example on Zalando)? Visual search for fashion, the task of identifying fashion articles in an image and finding them in an online store, has been the subject of an ever growing body of scientific literature over the last few years, and has been offered by many fashion stores.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generative Fashion Design</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/project/generative_design/generative_design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/project/generative_design/generative_design/</guid>
      <description>Team members:  Gökhan Yildirim  What is the fastest way to visually communicate a new design? Searching for similar-looking clothes? Drawing a sketch? Or creating a 3D representation on a computer program? Although all of them are viable solutions, they are quite time consuming.
At Zalando, we target an agile design process that combines invaluable human experience with the power of Machine Learning (ML). In particular, we do research on novel ways to use generative models in fashion design for rapid visualizations and prototyping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Time Series Modelling</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/project/probabilistic_timeseries_modelling/probabilistic_timeseries_modelling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/project/probabilistic_timeseries_modelling/probabilistic_timeseries_modelling/</guid>
      <description>Research Project by Ingmar Schuster, Kashif Rasul, Urs Bergmann, Calvin Seward, &amp;amp; Roland Vollgraf This project aims at probabilistic time series models, which is a general problem setting across many modern internet companies. In other words, we want to be capable of getting a predictive distribution for the value of a time series at future time points from our model. Such solutions are widely applicable to a number of Zalando use cases for example demand and trend forecasting or detecting anomalous behaviour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fashion MNIST</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/project/fashion_mnist/fashion_mnist/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/project/fashion_mnist/fashion_mnist/</guid>
      <description>Research Project by Kashif Rasul, Han Xiao (ex-member) &amp;amp; Roland Vollgraf Fashion-MNIST is a dataset of Zalando&amp;rsquo;s article images consisting of a training set of 60,000 examples and a test set of 10,000 examples. Each example is a 28x28 grayscale image, associated with a label from 10 classes. Fashion-MNIST is intended to serve as a direct drop-in replacement of the original MNIST dataset for benchmarking machine learning algorithms. Why is this of interest for the scientific community?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forecasting the customer’s preference</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/project/forecasting_the_customers_preference/forecasting_the_customers_preference/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/project/forecasting_the_customers_preference/forecasting_the_customers_preference/</guid>
      <description>Research Project by Christian Bracher &amp;amp; Sebastian Heinz We study time series of interactions of articles (fashion items) with customers. Our focus lies on personalized data, meaning, that each time series collects data for a single customer only. Examples include the customer’s purchase history as well as their click chain through the product detail pages in the shop. Our aim is to build a method which takes the past of a time series as input and effectively forecasts future events – the task of a recommender system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generative Models Research</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/project/generative_models_research/generative_models_research/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/project/generative_models_research/generative_models_research/</guid>
      <description>Research Project by Urs Bergmann (ex member), Nikolay Jetchev &amp;amp; Roland Vollgraf The overarching goal of this project is to advance the field of generative modeling, i.e. to build methods that learn complex probability distributions. In particular, we focus on generative adversarial networks (GANs), a relatively new technique that has shown impressive results in purely data-driven modeling of images.Texture created by Zalando Research method: We have developed a novel method for texture synthesis called Spatial-GAN, or SGAN.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://research.zalando.com/project/deeplearning/deeplearning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 16:10:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://research.zalando.com/project/deeplearning/deeplearning/</guid>
      <description>Et sensus uncos Troiaeque mori candidaque ostentis Litusque praemia Lorem markdownum natus, regis cecidere. Sinebat pudoris terque si commune pendebat ubi dubio cibique pontum virentem Nestora gaudia decebat quoniam eunt: graves. Teleste est colebat iamque ullis terra neque limen Nabataeus viribus ait.
encoding_install_autoresponder = ultra.osiComputer(host.ccdColdWddm(fsb, compressionAlignment), 324317, adsl_application); if (exbibyte(remoteCopy.pplVirtualUrl(3, hardOopBoot), solid, 46)) { eide_podcast(trinitron.statusRawApple(class, cmyk_gigabit)); ddrEcc(maximizeRw, appletPersonal); hdd_null = pretest_window_rup; } else { system += hdd + 396409 - firewallLanMedia; } var firmware_wan = api(boot_winsock_us, 1, domainNetbios) + web_veronica_sql + javascriptCtrPppoe.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
